Okay, so everyone we have done with the changes in this site bar dot JSX file, so you can have a look on this file, so basically what we have actually done is we have imported like users and get users from the chat store, and we are using this use effect hook from the React in order to just display and we have just passed this get users as a dependency array inside of this use effect hook and whatever changes.
Here, as you can see here, if the user's length equals to equals to zero means, I mean users length is zero then that case we can say that there's no contact founds, okay, otherwise we are going to take these users and for each user we are going to map this button and all the components and we are going to display from the users whatever the profile picture they have like user dot profile pick and and and from this span here.
User dot user name, okay, so in that component, so let's test this one out, so let's go to that site, so log out, so we are going to use this.
If I guess I queue at the rate of whatever the sample may least let's log in now as we can see that in the left hand side this online status is showing and along with that this profile, so but the thing is the profile is actually why it is not showing the thing is that we haven't updated the profile pictures for the earlier users right, so that's why but for ourselves we have updated it.
So we can just log out, so this is working correctly so log out successful now let's do proceed with the next steps.
So now go to this components.
Now, where is that yeah components in the components we can just make some few files like chat let's start with chat container because we are going to make that one so chat can.
Container dot jsex and const wait a second.
Chat can tater equals to use the callback function and now inside of this return dev.
Wait a second guys last and chat container let us export this so export default chat container, so chat container, so chat container is there so after this we are going to make few components like chat header also right.
So in this component let's make another file which is called as chat.
Head dot jsex so now for this chat header dot jsex same thing we are going to do okay so const.
Chat header equals to return dev chat header and export default chat header.
Now for chat container chat header and.
We are going to make the components for messages also right so message.
Yes dot jsex so const.
And return once simple dev called messages export.
Export default.
Messages.
One second export default messages okay so there would be messages right.
After this one more component which is message input so message input dot jsex so const.
Which import equals to one return dev message input.
Export a default message input okay so we have done for this also and for all of these components.
We can go inside of the chat container okay so in the chat container.
Okay return statement would be there and we have to display all of these multiple components so.
Take one dev as parent inside of the dev we are going to display all of the three components okay so chat header.
And after this message messages.
First would be the chat header component then messages and then the message input so whatever the message we are going to send would be inside of this message input.
And if you want we can import all of the three so import messages and.
Import message input controller safe now we have for both of these three.
So now let's go to the home page and we are displaying the sidebar here so after this sidebar we are going to display the container okay so can chat container chat container we are going to import and.
Now let's keep this some styles okay so tip class name.
Next row.
And it should be rounded large shadow.
Let's remove shadow don't need shadow which should be full and height we can set this as.
Which it would be fine I guess.
Okay so these are the styles which we have done it for and since it's a multiple component please make sure to add this inside of.
What we can actually do is we can wrap this container also also main class name equals to let's give it some style so flex one and background we would give as.
Okay so I think this is enough so in the next video we are going to configure some more changes so it's quite a long video so.
Okay I'm going to see you in the next video.